Guide to the Al Silverman Papers 1951-2003 MSS 136
© 2012 Fales Library and Special Collections
Al Silverman Papers
1951-2003
MSS 136
© 2012 Fales Library and Special Collections
23.5 linear feet
The Al Silverman Papers document the working life and activities of sports writer Al Silverman, author of ten books and numerous essays. The collection includes materials related to Al Silverman's work as an author as well as his work as editor of Sport Magazine, editor and publisher at Viking Press, and CEO and chairman of Book of the Month Club. Included in these files are draft copies of articles and books, research, interviews, magazine and newspaper clippings, correspondence with editors, and fan mail.
Silverman, Al
Provenance
The Al Silverman papers were donated by Al Silverman in 1998. Accretions were added to the collection in 2004 and 2009.
Access Restrictions
Restrictions are in place for a small portion of the collection. The Book of the Month Club meeting minutes are closed until 2023. Audiovisual materials have not been preserved and are not available to researchers. Appointments are necessary to consult manuscript and archival materials.
Biographical Note
Al Silverman, a noted sports writer, is author of 10 books and numerous essays published in, among other publications, Playboy, Saga, and Sport Magazine. Among his publications is I am Third, written with Gale Sayers, which became the acclaimed movie, "Brian's Song."
In addition to his writing, Silverman also worked as an editor and publisher. He was editor of Sport Magazine from 1951 to 1963 and was CEO and chairman of Book of the Month Club from 1972 to 1988. Most recently, Silverman served as editor and publisher at Viking Press from 1989 to 1997.
Scope and Content Note
This collection includes materials related to Al Silverman's work as an author as well as his work as editor of Sport Magazine, editor and publisher at Viking Press, and CEO and chairman of Book of the Month Club. Included in these files are draft copies of articles and books, research, interviews, magazine and newspaper clippings, correspondence with editors, and fan mail. The collected materials illustrate the stages of Silverman's writing process.
Most materials are in original format.
SERIES DESCRIPTIONS
SERIES I: Author Files
This series includes materials from several stages of Silverman's career including materials related to his work as an essayist and book author as well as his work as an editor of Sport Magazine and editor and publisher at Viking Press. Included are drafts, correspondence with editors, fan mail, interviews, research notes, contracts and audiocassettes.
Subseries A: Paper Files
Subseries B: Audio Recordings removed from Paper Files
Subseries C: Recorded Interviews
SERIES II: Book of the Month Club Files
Subseries A: Paper Files
Subseries B: Videocassettes
This series includes materials from Silverman's tenure as CEO and chairman of Book of the Month Club. Included are correspondence, press clippings and videocassettes as well as files related to Book of the Month Club: Sixty Years of Books in American Life, edited by Silverman.
SERIES III: It's Not Over 'Til It's Over
Subseries A: Paper Files
Subseries B: Books
Subseries C: Media
Subseries D: Digital Data Storage
This series is a 2004 accretion to the Al Silverman papers. It includes research materials for, and drafts of It's Not Over 'Til It's Over, a sports history book written by Silverman, published in 2002.
Arrangement
The Al Silverman Papers are organized into three series: Author Files, Book of the Month Club files, and "It's Not Over 'Til It's Over" materials. Within series I and II, files are organized chronologically. The files are in the original order in series III. Descriptions are at the folder level.
The files are grouped into 3 series:
I: Author Files
II: Book of the Month Club Files
III: It's Not Over 'Til it's Over
Separated Material
Over 800 books from Al Silverman's personal library were donated with his personal papers. An "author" or "related name" search in Bobcat, NYU's online catalog, will retrieve the records for the books.
Bellow, Saul; Book-of-the-Month Club.; Caro, Robert; Charles C. Little and James Brown (Firm).; Creative Television Association.; Daedalus (Boston, Mass.) .; DiMaggio, Joe, 1914-1999; Foster, Gregory, 1949-1972; Gottlieb, Robert, 1931-; Hornung, Paul, 1935-; Howard, Maureen, 1930-; Joyce, James, 1882-1941; Kennedy, Joseph P., (Joseph Patrick), 1888-1969; Laurie, Adelaide; Laurie, Rocco, 1948-1972; Liberty Magazine.; Mailer, Norman; McGinnis, Joe, 1954-; Piccolo, Brian, 1943-1970; Playboy Enterprises.; Robinson, Frank, 1935-; Saga.; Savago, Joe; Sayers, Gale, 1943-; Scholastic Inc..; Smith, Amanda; Sport Magazine.; Thomas, Lewis, 1913-1993; Tuchman, Barbara Wertheim; Updike, John; Viking Press.; American literature |y 20th century |x History and criticism.; Audiocassettes.; Book |v Reviews |z United States.; Books and reading |z United States |x History |y 20th century.; Clippings (information artifacts); Contracts.; Correspondence.; Manuscripts for publication.; Notebooks.; Photographs.; Sports journalism |z United States.; Sports |x History |v Periodicals.; Transcripts.; Videocassettes.
- Series I: Author Files
  - Subseries A: Paper Files
    Scope and Contents note
    This subseries includes drafts of Silverman's books; drafts and copies of articles; and correspondence, fan mail and photographs related to these writings. Also included are correspondence, contracts and reviews from his tenure at Sport Magazine and Viking Press.
    - Sport Magazine, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Sport Magazine, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Sport Magazine, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Sport Magazine, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Freelance Writing, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Freelance Writing, 1955-1956 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Freelance Writing, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Freelance Writing, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Freelance Writing, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Freelance Writing, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Freelance Writing, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Sport Magazine & Saga, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Photographs from Sport Magazine, 1961-1971 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Sport Magazine & Saga, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Sport Magazine, Saga & Playboy, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Saga & Playboy, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Fan Mail on Books, 1964-1985 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Sport Magazine & Playboy, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Paul Hornung: Football and the Single Man (the transcribed tapes), 1965 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Football and the Single Man (the transcribed tapes), 1965 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Football and the Single Man (the transcribed tapes), 1965 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Football and the Single Man (the transcribed tapes), 1965 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Football and the Single Man (final draft to printer), 1965 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Football and the Single Man (final draft to printer), 1965 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Football and the Single Man (correspondence, clippings), 1965 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Football and the Single Man (promotion, reviews, fan mail, clippings), 1965 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Sport Magazine & Scholastic Books, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Stories from Liberty Magazine Archives (some reprinted in Sport), 1966-1967 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Sport Magazine & Scholastic Books, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Sport Magazine & Scholastic Books, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Frank Robinson: My Life is Baseball (contract correspondence, reviews), 1968 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - My Life is Baseball (drafts of book's first and last chapters, clippings and Silverman's score cards), 1968 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - My Life is Baseball (chapters 2 & 3 drafts, clippings), 1968 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - My Life is Baseball (chapter draft - Rookie, clippings), 1968 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - My Life is Baseball (chapters 4 & 5 drafts, tape transcriptions, clippings), 1968 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - My Life is Baseball (chapters 8, 9 & 10 drafts, tapes, clippings), 1968 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - My Life is Baseball (chapters 11 & 12 drafts, tapes, clippings), 1968 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - My Life is Baseball (chapters 13 & 14 drafts, tapes, clippings), 1968 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - My Life is Baseball (chapters 15 & 16 drafts, tapes, clippings), 1968 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - My Life is Baseball (chapter 17 draft, tapes, clippings), 1968 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - My Life is Baseball (complete chapter drafts), 1968 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - My Life is Baseball (transcriptions of the tapes), 1968 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - My Life is Baseball (transcriptions of the tapes), 1968 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - My Life is Baseball (manuscript sent to printer), 1968 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - My Life is Baseball (manuscript sent to printer), 1968 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - My Life is Baseball (tape transcriptions, typed interviews, Robinson on race and NLVS), 1968 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - My Life is Baseball (clippings, photos), 1968 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - My Life is Baseball (proofs - reader's set), 1968 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - My Life is Baseball (index cards and notebooks), 1968 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Sport Magazine & Scholastic, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Joe DeMaggio: The Golden Year (correspondence, reviews, cancelled checks made out to Joe DeMaggio), 1969 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - The Golden Year (copyedited manuscript), 1969 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - The Golden Year (copyedited manuscript), 1969 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - The Golden Year ( final draft), 1969 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - The Golden Year (final copy, manuscript), 1969 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - The Golden Year (interviews with DeMaggio, magazine pieces), 1969 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - The Golden Year (research by chapter), 1969 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - The Golden Year (research), 1969 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - The Golden Year (research), 1969 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - The Golden Year (research), 1969 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - The Golden Year (interview book, stats, questions), 1969 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Sport Magazine & Playboy, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Gayle Sayers: I Am Third, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Gayle Sayers: I Am Third, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Gayle Sayers: I Am Third, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - I Am Third (addenda, reprints, contracts, royalties, letters, clippings), 1970 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - I Am Third ( Brian's Song - film of Sayers/Piccolo Friendship), 1970 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Piccolo (research), 1970 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - I Am Third (research), 1970 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - I Am Third (research), 1970 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - I Am Third (research), 1970 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - I Am Third (research), 1970 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - I Am Third (research), 1970 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - I Am Third (drafts, part I), 1970 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - I Am Third (drafts, part II), 1970 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - I Am Third/ Brian's Song (reviews), 1970 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - I Am Third (publishing, correspondence, letters on book), 1970 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - I Am Third (interview questions, notes), 1970 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Gayle Sayers: I Am Third, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Gayle Sayers: I Am Third, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Sport Magazine & Playboy, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Sport Magazine & Playboy, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Sport Magazine, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Sport Magazine, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Foster and Laurie (proposal, contracts production correspondence), 1974 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Foster and Laurie (9th precinct interviews), 1974 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Foster and Laurie (9th precinct interviews, transcriptions), 1974 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Foster and Laurie (partners - interviews), 1974 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Foster and Laurie (police academy - tape transcriptions, drafts), 1974 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Foster and Laurie (Adelaide Laurie interviews), 1974 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Foster and Laurie (widows - tape transcriptions, 2 early drafts), 1974 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Foster and Laurie (draft, part I), 1974 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Foster and Laurie (correspondence with widows and mother of son killed in Vietnam), 1974 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Foster and Laurie (widows at the hospital), 1974 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Foster and Laurie (East Village - interviews, map of the 9th precinct), 1974 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Foster and Laurie (cops reenactment - transcribed tapes, early drafts), 1974 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Foster and Laurie (murder night - transcribed, early drafts of chapters 1, 2, 3), 1974 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Foster and Laurie (Jackie Foster interviews), 1974 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Foster and Laurie (Adelaide Laurie - interviews), 1974 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Foster and Laurie (draft part V & epilogue), 1974 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Foster and Laurie (courtships, wedding - interviews, draft), 1974 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Foster and Laurie (Adelaide Laurie - early life - tapes transcribed with her inlaws), 1974 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Foster and Laurie (arrests of suspects), 1974 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Foster and Laurie (commemorative ceremonies, letters to widows from third grade class), 1974 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Foster and Laurie (manhunt begins - transcribed 9th precinct - cops, suspects, etc.), 1974 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Foster and Laurie (funeral - Foster - St. Pat's), 1974 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Foster and Laurie (funeral - Laurie - Staten Island), 1974 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Foster and Laurie (various revisions), 1974 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Foster and Laurie (Foster - Vietnam - early drafts, interviews, correspondence), 1974 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Foster and Laurie (draft part III, IV), 1974 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Foster and Laurie (Laurie - Vietnam - early drafts, interviews, correspondence), 1974 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Foster and Laurie (cont. Laurie - Vietnam), 1974 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Foster and Laurie (part II draft), 1974 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Foster and Laurie (correspondence, promotion, photographs, book reviews, movie reviews), 1974 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Foster and Laurie (the teleplay), 1974 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Foster and Laurie (movie deal), 1974 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Foster and Laurie (notebooks, index cards, references, quotations), 1974 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Foster and Laurie (interview questions - index cards), 1974 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Foster and Laurie (photographs of memorial service one year afterdeaths, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Foster and Laurie (copy to printer), 1974 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Foster and Laurie (copy to printer), 1974 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Foster and Laurie (duplicate galleys), 1974 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Sport Magazine, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Frank Robinson: My Life is Baseball The Revised Edition (new preface and afterward), 1975 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - The Viking Years (correspondence, reviews, National Book Awards), 1989 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - 20th Century Treasury of Sports (correspondence), 1989 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - The Viking Years (correspondence, reviews, National Book Awards), 1990 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - 20th Century Treasury of Sports (correspondence), 1990 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - The Viking Years (correspondence, reviews), 1991 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - 20th Century Treasury of Sports (correspondence), 1991 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - The Viking Years (correspondence, reviews, copies of James Joyce contract), 1992 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - 20th Century Treasury of Sports (correspondence, contract), 1992 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - 20th Century Treasury of Sports (promotion, reviews, letters from authors, head notes, filler), 1992 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - 20th Century Treasury of Sports (copy to printer), 1992 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - 20th Century Treasury of Sports (copy to printer), 1992 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - 20th Century Treasury of Sports (copy to printer), 1992 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - 20th Century Treasury of Sports (copy to printer), 1992 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - 20th Century Treasury of Sports (copy to printer), 1992 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - 20th Century Treasury of Sports (copy to printer), 1992 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - The Viking Years (correspondence, reviews, London trips), 1993 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - The Viking Years (correspondence, reviews), 1994 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - The Viking Years (correspondence), 1995 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - The Viking Years (correspondence), 1996 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - The Viking Years (correspondence), 1997 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Post Viking Years (correspondence), 1998 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Post Viking Years (correspondence), 1999 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Editing with Amanda Smith on Letters of her grandfather, Joseph Kennedy, 1994-2000 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Post Viking (contract for Letters of Joseph P. Kennedy w/ Amanda Smith), 1997 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Post Viking (correspondence, misc.), 2000 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Post Viking (correspondence, misc.), 2001 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Sayers: Introduction for New Edition I Am Third (drafts, correspondence), 2001-2002 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Post Viking (correspondence, misc.), 2002 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Post Viking (correspondence, misc.), 2003 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Paul Horning: Football and the Single Man (Look Magazine) [FLAT BOX], 1965 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Gayle Sayers: I Am Third - research [FLAT BOX], 1970 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Gayle Sayers, Brian Piccolo [FLAT BOX], 1970 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Subseries B: Audio Recordings removed from Paper Files
    Scope and Content
    This subseries contains audio recordings of interviews and other research materials which were removed from the paper portion of this series.
    Conditions Governing Access
    Audiovisual materials have not been preserved and are not available to researchers.
    - The Golden Year - Joe DeMaggio, 1969 (Box 8, Media ID: 136.0001)
    - The Golden Year - Joe DeMaggio, 1969 (Box 8, Media ID: 136.0002)
  - Subseries C: Recorded Interviews
    This subseries contains audiocassettes of recorded interviews done as research for Football and the Single Man, My Life is Baseball, I Am Third and Foster and Laurie.
    - Paul Hornung - 1 & 2, Early Life Plus High School, Sound recording, ¼ inch audiotape, 7.5 ips, 5 in. reel, Audio Magnetics., 1965 (Box 8, Media ID: 136.0003)
    - Paul Hornung - 3 & 4, Sound recording, ¼ inch audiotape, 7.5 ips, 5 in. reel, Audio Magnetics., 1965 (Box 8, Media ID: 136.0004)
    - Paul Hornung - 5 & 6, Sound recording, ¼ inch audiotape, 7.5 ips, 5 in. reel, Audio Magnetics., 1965 (Box 8, Media ID: 136.0005)
    - Paul Hornung - Paul Forgot to Give to You, Sound recording, ¼ inch audiotape, 7.5 ips, 5 in. reel, Audio Magnetics., 1965 (Box 8, Media ID: 136.0006)
    - Paul Hornung - Mother Completed, Sound recording, ¼ inch audiotape, 5 in. reel, [Brand unidentified]., 1965 (Box 8, Media ID: 136.0007)
    - Paul Hornung - Mrs. Hornung, Sound recording, ¼ inch audiotape, 7.5 ips, 5 in. reel, Scotch., 1965 (Box 8, Media ID: 136.0008)
    - Paul Hornung - Miami, Hornung one side only, Sound recording, ¼ inch audiotape, 7.5 ips, 5 in. reel, Audio Magnetics., 1965 (Box 8, Media ID: 136.0009)
    - Paul Hornung - [unlabeled], Sound recording, ¼ inch audiotape, 7.5 ips, 5 in. reel, Audio Magnetics., 1965 (Box 8, Media ID: 136.0010)
    - Paul Hornung - [unlabeled], Sound recording, ¼ inch audiotape, 5 in. reel, [Brand unidentified]., 1965 (Box 8, Media ID: 136.0011)
    - Frank Robinson - A, 61-62[?], Sound recording, 1.4 in. tape, 5 in. reel, Lafayette., 1968 (Box 8, Media ID: 136.0012)
    - Frank Robinson - B Sound recording, 1.4 in. tape, 5 in. reel, Lafayette., 1968 (Box 8, Media ID: 136.0013)
    - Frank Robinson, C Sound recording, 1.4 in. tape, 5 in. reel, Tempo., 1968 (Box 8, Media ID: 136.0014)
    - Frank Robinson - 1&2, '66 Trade, Sound recording, 1.4 in. tape, 5 in. reel, Lafayette., 1968 (Box 8, Media ID: 136.0015)
    - Frank Robinson - 3&4, 1966 Season, Sound recording, 1.4 in. tape, 5 in. reel, Lafayette., 1968 (Box 8, Media ID: 136.0016)
    - Frank Robinson - 5&6, early days, through high school, 3 first half 17/8, Sound recording, 1.4 in. tape, 5 in. reel, Lafayette., 1968 (Box 8, Media ID: 136.0017)
    - I Am Third - through high school with Linda (transcribed), 1&2, Sound recording, audiocassette, Norelco, C-120., 1970 (Box 8, Media ID: 136.0018)
    - I Am Third - high school, recruiting, Linda, 3&4, Sound recording, audiocassette, Norelco, C-120., 1970 (Box 8, Media ID: 136.0019)
    - I Am Third - Linda & Gale, marriage quarrels, scrapbooks, Paine Webber 5&6, Sound recording, audiocassette, Norelco, C-120., 1970 (Box 8, Media ID: 136.0020)
    - I Am Third - Tommy Dare, Gale Sat College, Caine Webber, 9&10, Sound recording, audiocassette, Norelco, C-120., 1970 (Box 8, Media ID: 136.0021)
    - I Am Third - College, 11&12, Sound recording, audiocassette, Norelco, C-120., 1970 (Box 8, Media ID: 136.0022)
    - I Am Third - 13&14, Sound recording, audiocassette, Norelco, C-120., 1970 (Box 8, Media ID: 136.0023)
    - I Am Third - 65, 66 season, 67, 15&16, season Brake interview, Sound recording, audiocassette, Norelco, C-120., 1970 (Box 8, Media ID: 136.0024)
    - I Am Third - 1969 Brake interview, 1969 Season, Pick, 17&18, Sound recording, audiocassette, Norelco, C-120., 1970 (Box 8, Media ID: 136.0025)
    - I Am Third - Mike Shinn, 20&21 Sound recording, audiocassette, Norelco, C-120., 1970 (Box 8, Media ID: 136.0026)
    - I Am Third - Mellen Interview, Easton Interview, Roger Sayers, 20&21, Sound recording, audiocassette, Norelco, C-120., 1970 (Box 8, Media ID: 136.0027)
    - I Am Third - 1968, Misc., 22&23, Sound recording, audiocassette, Norelco, C-120., 1970 (Box 8, Media ID: 136.0028)
    - I Am Third - Misc. 1968 Knee, 1969 Season, 24&25, Sound recording, audiocassette, Norelco, C-120., 1970 (Box 8, Media ID: 136.0029)
    - I Am Third - Piccolo, 26&27, Sound recording, audiocassette, Norelco, C-120., 1970 (Box 8, Media ID: 136.0030)
    - I Am Third - 28&29, Sound recording, audiocassette, Norelco, C-120, 1970 (Box 8, Media ID: 136.0031)
    - I Am Third - Bill Cosby Intro, Fran Tarkenton, Sound recording, audiocassette, Scotch, C-120., 1970 (Box 8, Media ID: 136.0032)
    - Foster and Laurie - Mrs. Foster Feb. 12, '73, Sound recording, audiocassette, Capitol, C120., 1973 (Box 8, Media ID: 136.0033)
    - Foster and Laurie - conversation with Linda, Sound recording, audiocassette, Mercury, C-120., 1974 (Box 8, Media ID: 136.0034)
    - Foster and Laurie - Mrs. Foster, Sound recording, audiocassette, Memorex 120., 1974 (Box 8, Media ID: 136.0035)
    - Foster and Laurie - Sgt. Riede, Gunny Sgt. Gerald Lester, Sound recording, audiocassette, Memorex 120., 1974 (Box 8, Media ID: 136.0036)
    - Foster and Laurie - Mrs. Laurie, Sound recording, audiocassette, Memorex 120., 1974 (Box 8, Media ID: 136.0037)
    - Foster and Laurie - Anthony Laurie, Sound recording, audiocassette, Memorex 120., 1974 (Box 8, Media ID: 136.0038)
    - Foster and Laurie - Mrs. Laurie, Mrs. Foster, Sound recording, audiocassette, Memorex 120., 1974 (Box 8, Media ID: 136.0039)
    - Foster and Laurie - Adelaide, Family life, Sound recording, audiocassette, Memorex 120., 1974 (Box 8, Media ID: 136.0040)
    - Foster and Laurie - Mr. and Mrs. Jammateo (uncle, aunt Laurie), Sound recording, audiocassette, Memorex 120., 1974 (Box 8, Media ID: 136.0041)
    - Foster and Laurie - Mrs. Foster, Sound recording, audiocassette, Memorex 120., 1974 (Box 8, Media ID: 136.0042)
    - Foster and Laurie - Mr. and Mrs. A. Laurie, Mrs. Anthony Laurie, Sound recording, audiocassette, Memorex 120., 1974 (Box 8, Media ID: 136.0043)
    - Foster and Laurie - H-1, Sound recording, audiocassette, Phillips, C-90., 1974 (Box 8, Media ID: 136.0044)